# Natalie Man

hello@nataliehman.co.uk • linkedin.com/in/nataliehman • www.nataliehman.co.uk

## **UX Designer**

As a UX Designer with a front-end development background, I combine my interest in technology and problem-solving skills to create product experiences that meet business goals and user needs. I have collaborated with developers in an agile environment to understand technological capabilities and use design thinking to develop impactful solutions.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **UX Designer**

**UX Playground •** Jul 2018 - Present

- Supported the team in organising events and training for the design community, which grew by over 3,700 members in 3 years.
- Created content strategies, user flow diagrams, wireframes and prototypes for rebranding the company website, which increased visitor traffic from 60% to 151% within 6 months.
- Collaborated with the community founder on design research, and created presentations for design events such as Adobe MAX 2018, Brand Week Istanbul and Berlin Design Week.

# **UX Designer (Contract)**

Adobe • Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

- Collaborated with a Senior UX Designer to develop 2 "CMD+cause" remote design workshops for Adobe's enterprise customers. Each session had up to 100 registrations.
- Conducted research focused on collaborative design for helping Adobe's XDI team to teach and promote XD to its enterprise customers to increase software adoption.
- Created presentations in Adobe XD and prepared activities on audience engagement tools such as Mentimeter, which was utilised by Adobe's XDI team for running the workshop sessions.

## **UX Designer**

Smartology.net • Feb 2018 - Apr 2019

- Facilitated team ideation sessions with 11 people, including a product owner, account managers, and developers, which led to a redesigned dashboard to support the company's growth.
- Conducted 5 user interviews to identify the needs of internal users, and communicated these actionable insights to the development team for improving workflow efficiency.
- Organised user testing with the Lead Front-end Developer for an automated tool that helps account managers to efficiently create screenshots of ad campaigns for clients.

### **Front-End Developer**

Smartology.net • Nov 2014 - Feb 2018

- Managed over 60 client ad campaigns and designed over 2000 creative ads.
  Process includes research, creating mockups, managing client feedback, building and testing.
- Worked in a team of 3, and conducted peer reviews to assess the quality of ad campaigns before launching on media publishing websites such as Financial Times, BBC and Bloomberg.
- Developed the company's WordPress website with consistent branding, and created a process for the sales and marketing team to publish blog posts.

# Web/Graphic Designer and Marketing Assistant

GetOptics Group Ltd • Oct 2011 - Mar 2012

#### **SKILLS**

User testing, User research, Content strategy, Prototyping, User-centered Design, User interviews, Wireframing, Agile

#### **EDUCATION**

## Master of Arts - MA in Web Design & Content Planning

University of Greenwich • Sep 2012 - Jul 2014

# Bachelor of Science (BSc) in Computer Science

Queen Mary, University of London • Sep 2007 - Jul 2010